[Unexpected Falling]
[هبوط غير متوقع]
[Episode 37]
[الحلقة 37]
(For me,)
(لي،)
Tan Shen
تان شين
was my lifesaver.
كان منقذي.
Was posting the evidence of the affair
تم نشر دليل العلاقة
Tan Shen's idea?
فكرة تان شين؟
Zhu Xiaolei's lover
عاشق تشو Xiaolei
provoked me.
استفزني.
I lost it,
لقد فقدته،
so I posted
لذلك قمت بالنشر
all the evidence that Tan Shen
كل الأدلة على أن تان شين
helped me find online on impulse.
ساعدني في العثور على الإنترنت عند الاندفاع.
How was the talk?
كيف كان الحديث؟
You didn't just sympathize
أنت لم تتعاطف فقط
with An Ruiyun, did you?
مع An Ruiyun ، أليس كذلك؟
You had
عندك
some other feelings
بعض المشاعر الأخرى
for her.
لها.
Yes.
نعم.
She asked me to return this card to you
طلبت مني إعادة هذه البطاقة إليك
and said she doesn't need it.
وقالت إنها لا تحتاجها.
And she thanks you for taking care of Yiyi
وهي تشكرك على الاهتمام بـ Yiyi
for so many years.
لسنوات عديدة.
Also,
ايضا،
she asked me to tell you this.
طلبت مني أن أخبرك بهذا.
She said
قالت
Zhu Xiaolei
تشو شياولي
was irritated by her words
كان منزعجًا من كلماتها
that day.
ذلك اليوم.
It has nothing to do with you.
لا علاقة لك به.
It was me who irritated Zhu Xiaolei.
كنت أنا من أزعج Zhu Xiaolei.
I also hope
كما أتمنى
he can forgive me for my selfishness.
يمكنه أن يغفر لي أناني.
Go and say hello.
اذهب وقل مرحبا.
Get it.
احصل عليه.
Okay.
تمام.
You can't even get it.
لا يمكنك حتى الحصول عليه.
Why did you kick it over there?
لماذا ركلته هناك؟
How can you blame me?
كيف يمكنك أن تلومني؟
Don't you have anything to ask?
ليس لديك أي شيء تطلبه؟
Did you change your job
هل قمت بتغيير وظيفتك
because of An Ruiyun's case?
بسبب قضية أن رويون؟
I tend to
أنا أميل إلى
go to extremes.
تطرف.
And I don't like being controlled.
وأنا لا أحب أن أكون تحت السيطرة.
So I'm tired
لذلك أنا متعب
of being well-dressed
من حسن الملبس
and dealing
والتعامل
with people.
مع الناس.
It was the first time
كانت المرة الأولى
I faced my true self
واجهت نفسي الحقيقية
in An Ruiyun's case.
في قضية أن رويون.
It seems
يبدو
An Ruiyun herself
Ruiyun نفسها
made every decision in that case.
اتخذ كل قرار في هذه الحالة.
In fact,
في الواقع،
I'm behind all this.
أنا وراء كل هذا.
I made her more furious
جعلتها أكثر غضبا
and more extreme.
وأكثر تطرفا.
So I bear a huge responsibility
لذلك أنا أتحمل مسؤولية كبيرة
for that result.
لتلك النتيجة.
Do you
هل أنت
want to know what I think?
تريد أن تعرف ما هو رأيي؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Objective conditions
شروط موضوعية
do affect subjective consciousness.
لا تؤثر على الوعي الذاتي.
But what a person does
لكن ما يفعله الإنسان
in the end,
فى النهاية،
it depends on their consciousness,
يعتمد على وعيهم ،
doesn't it?
أليس كذلك؟
Prepare all the materials
تحضير جميع المواد
for the meeting later.
للاجتماع في وقت لاحق.
Rest assured.
اطمئن، لا تشغل بالك.
Why is she here?
لماذا هل هي هنا؟
I wonder too.
أتساءل أيضا.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Why? Don't you know me anymore?
لماذا ا؟  ألا تعرفني بعد الآن؟
Hello, Ms. Su Wen.
مرحبا ، السيدة سو ون.
I want to meet Fang Jianshe.
أريد أن أقابل فانغ جيانشي.
All right, Ms. Su.
حسنًا ، سيدة سو.
Please wait a moment.
فضلا انتظر لحظة.
We're also very cautious
نحن أيضًا حذرون جدًا
about the other party's
عن الطرف الآخر
second financing.
التمويل الثاني.
We've sent our professional staff there.
لقد أرسلنا موظفينا المحترفين إلى هناك.
The details
التفاصيل
are written in the report.
مكتوبة في التقرير.
All right. I'll have a look later.
حسنا.  سآخذ نظرة لاحقا.
Mr. Fang, Su Wen is here.
السيد فانغ ، سو ون هنا.
Su Wen?
سو ون؟
She's in the small meeting room.
إنها في غرفة الاجتماعات الصغيرة.
All right.
حسنا.
Okay.
تمام.
All right, I get it.
حسنًا ، فهمت.
All right. Please wait a minute.
حسنا.  من فضلك انتظر دقيقة.
Let me have a look.
دعني ألقي نظرة.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
This group is all automatic investment, right?
هذه المجموعة كلها استثمارات تلقائية ، أليس كذلك؟
Wait a minute. Let me confirm it.
انتظر دقيقة.  اسمحوا لي أن أؤكد ذلك.
Okay.
تمام.
Ms. Su, here's some water.
السيدة سو ، ها هي بعض الماء.
I'll hand it in first.
سأسلمها أولا.
Three with one.
ثلاثة مع واحد.
Follow.
يتبع.
One 2, huh?
واحد 2 ، هاه؟
Pass.
يمر.
Four 5s.
أربعة 5s.
[Shi Shengyu] A bomb.
[شي Shengyu] قنبلة.
Play it for me.
العبها لي.
Okay.
تمام.
Do you want to follow?
هل تريد المتابعة؟
Four 5s?
أربعة 5s؟
Come on.
هيا.
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Zhenzhen.
زينزين.
Hello, Zhenzhen.
مرحبًا ، Zhenzhen.
Well...
نحن سوف...
Ms. Su Wen suddenly came to Jinshang.
جاءت السيدة سو ون فجأة إلى جينشانغ.
Su Wen went to Jinshang?
ذهب سو ون إلى جينشانغ؟
Do you want to follow?
هل تريد المتابعة؟
Pass.
يمر.
You've got it.
لقد حصلت عليها.
[Chairman]
[رئيس]
What brings you here, Ms. Su Wen?
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا ، السيدة سو وين؟
[Letter of Accusation]
[خطاب الاتهام]
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
No hurry.
لا يتعجل.
Look carefully first.
انظر بعناية أولاً.
[Letter of Accusation]
[خطاب الاتهام]
All the materials
كل المواد
of both Jinshang and Anhe
لكل من جينشانغ وآنه
have been found.
تم العثور على.
It's not easy, right?
ليس من السهل ، أليس كذلك؟
Not really.
ليس صحيحا.
Did you get the wrong person?
هل حصلت على الشخص الخطأ؟
I specially brought it to you.
لقد أحضرته لك خصيصًا.
Would you please estimate the price?
هل تسمح من فضلك بتقدير السعر؟
You're blackmailing me.
أنت تبتزني.
Mr. Fang.
السيد فانغ.
Your words are not very accurate.
كلماتك ليست دقيقة للغاية.
How could it be blackmailing?
كيف يمكن أن يكون ابتزاز؟
Isn't it demanding bribes?
أليس طلب رشاوى؟
What happened before was a misunderstanding.
ما حدث من قبل كان سوء فهم.
Mr. Fang.
السيد فانغ.
I came all the way here.
جئت على طول الطريق هنا.
So don't brush me off.
لذا لا تتجاهلني.
All right.
حسنا.
Then follow the rules.
ثم اتبع القواعد.
Name your price.
حدد سعرك.
Hello, I'd like to ask...
مرحبًا ، أود أن أسأل ...
Zhenzhen.
زينزين.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
I was sent here to deal with something.
لقد تم إرسالي إلى هنا للتعامل مع شيء ما.
Time is running out,
الوقت ينفذ،
so I didn't tell you.
لذلك لم أخبرك.
What's the matter?
ما الأمر؟
Aren't you on vacation?
ألست في إجازة؟
It's an interim arrangement.
إنه ترتيب مؤقت.
You two are here to do something, aren't you?
أنتما الإثنان هنا لفعل شيئًا ، أليس كذلك؟
Then go ahead. Don't waste time.
إذن إمض قدما.  لا تضيعوا الوقت.
Let's get in touch.
دعونا الحصول على اتصال.
Let's talk outside.
لنتحدث في الخارج.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Give it to me.
اعطني اياه.
Why did you go to see Fang Jianshe?
لماذا ذهبت لرؤية فانغ جيانشي؟
Did you threaten him?
هل هددته؟
You're right.
أنت على حق.
I asked him for money.
طلبت منه المال.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
They set me up.
وضعوا لي.
I almost lost my reputation.
كدت أفقد سمعتي.
What's wrong with asking for compensation
ما الخطأ في طلب التعويض
for psychological injuries?
للإصابات النفسية؟
Shouldn't I do that?
ألا يجب أن أفعل ذلك؟
You're breaking the law.
أنت تخالف القانون.
Even if I break the law,
حتى لو خالفت القانون ،
does it have anything to do with you?
هل له علاقة بك؟
Are you a police officer or a judge?
هل أنت ضابط شرطة أم قاض؟
I don't want you to go astray.
لا أريدك أن تضل الطريق.
Go astray?
يضل؟
I have nowhere to go.
انا لا امتلك مكان لاذهب اليه.
Ruan Zhenzhen.
روان زينزين.
The kidney you gave me
الكلية التي أعطيتني إياها
will soon stop working.
سيتوقف عن العمل قريبًا.
Can you give me another one?
هل يمكنك أن تعطيني واحدة أخرى؟
Can you?
هل تستطيع؟
I need money.
أحتاج للمال.
I need money to survive.
احتاج المال للبقاء على قيد الحياة.
I haven't lived enough.
لم أعش بما فيه الكفاية.
Su Wen.
سو ون.
You're not this kind of person.
أنت لست من هذا النوع من الأشخاص.
I am this kind of person.
أنا هذا النوع من الأشخاص.
I don't want to die.
لا أريد أن أموت.
I want to live on.
اريد ان اعيش.
I don't want to lie in the hospital bed
لا أريد أن أستلقي على سرير المستشفى
waiting for a miracle.
في انتظار معجزة.
There's only one fool like you.
هناك أحمق واحد مثلك.
I'll never meet another one.
لن أقابل شخصًا آخر أبدًا.
Do you know
هل تعرف
what you're holding?
ماذا تحتجز؟
It's evidence
إنه دليل
that can bring Fang Jianshe down.
التي يمكن أن تسقط فانغ جيانش.
It's money.
إنه المال.
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
Give it to me.
اعطني اياه.
Let me go, okay?
دعني اذهب ، حسنا؟
It has
لديها
nothing to do with you.
لا يوجد شيئ لفعله معك.
Just pretend as if you know nothing.
فقط تظاهر وكأنك لا تعرف شيئًا.
Give it to me.
اعطني اياه.
Su Wen.
سو ون.
I only have you.
لا يوجد لي أحد سواك.
No matter what you do,
بغض النظر عن ما تفعله،
you can't fool me.
لا يمكنك أن تخدعني.
You want more money
تريد المزيد من المال
just to
فقط ل
pay my debts.
دفع ديوني.
Don't flatter yourself.
لا تملق نفسك.
It has nothing to do with you.
لا علاقة لك به.
But have you ever thought about it?
لكن هل فكرت في ذلك من قبل؟
Do you think I could take the money with ease
هل تعتقد أنه يمكنني أخذ المال بسهولة
if you give it to me?
إذا أعطيته لي؟
Ruan Zhenzhen.
روان زينزين.
Are you a fool?
هل انت مجنون؟
I can
أنا استطيع
handle it well.
تعامل معها بشكل جيد.
Not only can you pay off your debts,
لا يمكنك فقط سداد ديونك ،
but you also don't have to worry for the rest of your life.
ولكن لا داعي للقلق أيضًا لبقية حياتك.
Do you get it?
هل حصلت عليه؟
What about you?
وماذا عنك؟
I'm dying.
أنا أموت.
I won't live long.
لن أعيش طويلا.
You can't go.
لا يمكنك الذهاب.
[Police]
[شرطة]
[Reception Room]
[غرفة الاستقبال]
Let me go with you.
دعني اذهب معك.
No, I can do it myself.
لا ، يمكنني أن أفعل ذلك بنفسي.
Sir.
سيد.
Qiu.
تشيو.
All our efforts are in vain.
كل جهودنا تذهب سدى.
Sir.
سيد.
I didn't expect
لم أتوقع
that someone would take the video.
أن شخصًا ما سيأخذ الفيديو.
It's too late to say that.
لقد فات الأوان لقول ذلك.
I will have to sacrifice you.
سأضطر للتضحية بك.
I have no other choice.
ليس لدي أي خيار آخر.
It's good for you, me,
هذا جيد بالنسبة لي ،
and everyone.
وكل شخص.
As for your daughter
أما ابنتك
and your family,
و عائلتك،
I'll arrange for someone to take good care of them.
سأرتب لشخص يعتني بهم جيدًا.
Sir.
سيد.
Things are not as bad
الأمور ليست بهذا السوء
as we think.
كما نعتقد.
It's just a video.
إنه مجرد فيديو.
It can't prove anything.
لا يمكن إثبات أي شيء.
As for Su Wen,
أما بالنسبة لسو ون ،
it's easy to take care of her
من السهل الاعتناء بها
since she's asking for money.
منذ أن طلبت المال.
It's not about money.
الأمر لا يتعلق بالمال.
Giving her money will only bring endless trouble.
منحها المال لن يؤدي إلا إلى مشاكل لا نهاية لها.
Don't be so nervous.
لا تكن متوترا جدا.
After all,
بعد كل شيء،
it's an economic crime.
إنها جريمة اقتصادية.
You'll only be in prison for a few years.
ستظل في السجن لبضع سنوات فقط.
As long as I'm here,
طالما أنا هنا ،
I won't treat you unfairly.
لن أعاملك بشكل غير عادل.
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
We can gain the upper hand
يمكننا كسب اليد العليا
if we take the initiative now.
إذا أخذنا زمام المبادرة الآن.
Sorry for making you go through this.
آسف لجعلك تمر بهذا.
Sir.
سيد.
It's possible
انه ممكن
to escape punishment and commit suicide in such a situation.
للإفلات من العقاب والانتحار في مثل هذه الحالة.
But you won't.
لكنك لن تفعل.
Because you're smart.
لأنك ذكي.
Right?
حق؟
I get it, sir.
فهمت يا سيدي.
Eight.
ثمانية.
Q.
س.
One K.
واحد ك.
Pass.
يمر.
One 2.
واحد 2.
Su Wen.
سو ون.
Did you go to Jinshang?
هل ذهبت إلى جينشانغ؟
Yes.
نعم.
How did it go?
كيف سار الأمر؟
Yan Xiaowen.
يان شياووين.
Turn yourself in.
تسلم نفسك.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
You're burning bridges, aren't you?
أنت تحرق الجسور ، أليس كذلك؟
Hey!
يا!
(Hello.)
(مرحبًا.)
(The number)
(الرقم)
(you have dialed is engaged.)
(قمت بالاتصال مخطوب.)
(Please try later.)
(يرجى المحاولة لاحقًا.)
Why did I believe you?
لماذا صدقتك
Su Wen!
سو ون!
One 2.
واحد 2.
Pass.
يمر.
One 6.
واحد 6.
One Q.
سؤال واحد.
Pass. Your turn.
يمر.  دورك.
Your turn.
دورك.
Thank you, Boss.
شكرا لك يا رئيس.
-Five 5s. -Did you put chili?
-خمسة 5s.  هل وضعت الفلفل الحار؟
Yes.
نعم.
What was it?
ماذا كان؟
Five 5s.
خمسة 5s.
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
One A.
واحد أ.
-Pass. -No.
-يمر.  -رقم.
Shall we go and check on her?
هل نذهب ونفحصها؟
Just leave her alone for a while.
فقط اتركها بمفردها لفترة من الوقت.
Sometimes,
بعض الأحيان،
something can only
شيء يمكن فقط
be faced
سيواجهها
and digested by oneself.
وهضمه نفسه.
No matter
لا يهم
how close you are,
ما مدى قربك ،
you can't share the burden.
لا يمكنك تقاسم العبء.
Are you comprehending life?
هل تفهم الحياة؟
Sort of.
نوعا ما.
Life is unpredictable.
الحياة لا يمكن التنبؤ بها.
You never know
أنت لا تعرف أبدا
what will happen in the future.
ماذا سيحدث في المستقبل.
There are too many unpredictable things.
هناك الكثير من الأشياء التي لا يمكن التنبؤ بها.
But there are also
ولكن هناك أيضًا
many unexpected things in life.
أشياء كثيرة غير متوقعة في الحياة.
Don't be so pessimistic.
لا تكن متشائما جدا.
Be positive.
كن ايجابيا.
It could be a good thing
يمكن أن يكون شيء جيد
or a disaster.
أو كارثة.
But no matter what happens,
لكن مهما حدث ،
we have to face it.
علينا مواجهته.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
Where are you going?
إلى أين تذهب؟
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I'm giving them a hand.
أنا أقدم لهم يد المساعدة.
Sit down. Are you a fool?
اجلس.  هل انت مجنون؟
Sit down.
اجلس.
You're so oblivious.
أنت غافل جدا.
I'm not a match for you two. I quit.
أنا لست مباراة لكما.  أنسحب.
Mr. Xiao.
السيد شياو.
We had a deal.
اتفقنا.
How can you stand me up?
كيف يمكنك الوقوف لي؟
I know you're busy.
أعلم أنك مشغول.
When will you be free, then?
متى ستكون حرا اذا؟
Okay.
تمام.
I'll wait to hear from you.
سأنتظر لسماع منك.
Okay. Bye.
تمام.  وداعا.
He said he couldn't come
قال إنه لا يستطيع المجيء
because of something urgent.
بسبب شيء عاجل.
Jianshe.
جيانش.
Why are you looking
لماذا تبحث
for a helmsman in such a hurry?
لقائد الدفة في عجلة من هذا القبيل؟
Isn't it too worthy for him?
ألا تستحقه أكثر من اللازم؟
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
How can I
كيف يمكنني
read your mind, Mr. Fang?
اقرأ أفكارك يا سيد فانغ؟
I heard
سمعت
that something happened to Qiu Zhijian.
أن شيئًا ما حدث لـ Qiu Zhijian.
They can't reach him on his phone.
لا يمكنهم الوصول إليه على هاتفه.
Who told you that?
من قال لك ذلك؟
It's just
انه فقط
a gust of wind
عاصفة من الرياح
coming to me.
تعال الي.
The inspection team found a small problem.
وجد فريق التفتيش مشكلة صغيرة.
It's no big deal.
ليس بالأمر الجلل.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
You found him?
هل وجدته؟
Okay.
تمام.
No hurry.
لا يتعجل.
Do it after dark.
افعلها بعد حلول الظلام.
Don't let Xia
لا تدع شيا
run away this time.
اهرب هذه المرة.
Who are you scheming against again?
من الذي تتآمر ضده مرة أخرى؟
A nobody.
لا أحد.
Not worth mentioning.
لا يستحق الذكر.
You play first.
أنت تلعب أولا.
I'm going to the washroom.
انا ذاهب الى الحمام.
Okay.
تمام.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
You'd better leave now.
من الأفضل أن تغادر الآن.
Fang already knows
يعرف فانغ بالفعل
where you are.
أين أنت.
(If Boss doesn't want you to leave,)
(إذا كان الرئيس لا يريدك أن تغادر ،)
none of you can get away.
لا أحد منكم يمكنه الابتعاد.
Do you understand?
هل تفهم؟
Yes.
نعم.
Do you really understand?
هل تفهم حقا
It's simple.
انه سهل.
You caused the trouble.
لقد تسببت في المتاعب.
Boss won't let you go
لن يسمح لك الرئيس بالرحيل
if you
اذا أنت
don't handle it well.
لا تتعامل معها بشكل جيد.
You can't let the trouble
لا يمكنك ترك المتاعب
get him in trouble.
يوقعه في مأزق.
No.
رقم.
Please tell the boss
من فضلك أخبر رئيسك
that I won't
لن أفعل
get him in trouble.
يوقعه في مأزق.
Are you sure?
هل أنت واثق؟
It's obvious.
من الواضح.
If the sparks can't be put out,
إذا كان لا يمكن إخماد الشرر ،
it'll get to our boss.
سيصل إلى رئيسنا.
Secretary Chen.
وزير تشن.
It's not
ليست كذلك
that I don't want to snuff the sparks out.
أنني لا أريد أن أشم الشرر.
Nobody dares to kill anyone
لا أحد يجرؤ على قتل أحد
in this situation,
في هذا الوضع،
no matter how much money you offer.
بغض النظر عن مقدار المال الذي تقدمه.
You can do it yourself.
تستطيع فعلها بنفسك.
You can leave
تستطيع الرحيل
if you get things done.
إذا أنجزت الأمور.
Didn't I tell you to wait outside?
ألم أقل لك أن تنتظر بالخارج؟
There are more people outside.
هناك المزيد من الناس في الخارج.
Now besides the police,
الآن بجانب الشرطة ،
Fang is looking for you too.
فانغ يبحث عنك ايضا
Make sure you hide well.
تأكد من أنك تختبئ جيدًا.
Don't contact me for the time being.
لا تتصل بي في الوقت الحاضر.
I'll send you out
سأرسل لك
when I find someone.
عندما أجد شخص ما.
That's all?
هذا كل شئ؟
Who still
من لا يزال
carries cash now?
يحمل النقود الآن؟
You can only withdraw 20,000 yuan a day from an ATM.
يمكنك فقط سحب 20000 يوان في اليوم من أجهزة الصراف الآلي.
How many days can I live with this little money?
كم يوما يمكنني العيش مع هذا القليل من المال؟
Bear it for a few days.
تحملها لبضعة أيام.
You can spend the money
يمكنك انفاق المال
as you please
كما تريد
after going out.
بعد الخروج.
The password is on the back of it.
كلمة المرور على ظهرها.
Is Fang's twenty million yuan in it?
هل فانغ عشرين مليون يوان فيه؟
Why would I lie to you?
لماذا اكذب عليك؟
Keep it well.
احتفظ بها بشكل جيد.
Spend it after going out.
تنفقه بعد الخروج.
You'd better hurry up.
من الأفضل أن تسرع.
I'm more anxious than you.
أنا أكثر قلقا منك.
You should go now.
يجب أن تذهب الآن.
Be careful when you go out.
كن حذرا عندما تخرج.
Stay away from security cameras.
ابتعد عن كاميرات المراقبة.
Lu Yang doesn't even know
لو يانغ لا يعرف حتى
that I pretended to be Xu Youning.
أنني تظاهرت بأنني شو يونغ.
How did Fang know?
كيف عرف فانغ؟
How did he know where I was hiding?
كيف عرف أين كنت أختبئ؟
How do I know?
كيف أعرف؟
Anyway, he knew it now.
على أي حال ، كان يعرف ذلك الآن.
Oh, right.
صحيح.
Let me remind you.
دعني أذكرك.
Don't be obsessed with money
لا تكن مهووسًا بالمال
and mess with him again.
وعبث معه مرة أخرى.
What?
ماذا؟
Didn't we agree
ألم نتفق
to blackmail him as much as we can?
لابتزازه بقدر ما نستطيع؟
That was before.
هذا كان في السابق.
Now, things are different.
الآن ، الأمور مختلفة.
All right. Leave now.
حسنا.  ارحل الآن.
Why do you have to return
لماذا عليك العودة
to Guangzhou to cooperate with the investigation?
إلى قوانغتشو للتعاون مع التحقيق؟
They don't even tell you what's the investigation about.
إنهم لا يخبروك حتى عن سبب التحقيق.
What are you worried about?
ما الذي أنت قلق بشأنه؟
If it was an investigation against me,
إذا كان تحقيقا ضدي ،
they would have
سيكون لديهم
taken me away like last time.
أخذني بعيدًا مثل آخر مرة.
They wouldn't call me
لم يتصلوا بي
to tell me to go back.
ليقول لي أن أعود.
Since they called me,
منذ أن اتصلوا بي ،
it means it has nothing to do with me.
هذا يعني أنه لا علاقة لي به.
I guess
اعتقد
it has something to do
لديها ما تفعله
with Zhang Xiyao framing me.
مع Zhang Xiyao تأطير لي.
That girl
تلك الفتاة
is too bold.
جريئة جدا.
She has to be punished.
يجب أن تعاقب.
She's young, after all.
إنها شابة ، بعد كل شيء.
She has the capability.
لديها القدرة.
She went astray because she wanted to get promoted.
ضلّت الطريق لأنها أرادت أن تتم ترقيتها.
She can't harm others even so.
لا يمكنها أن تؤذي الآخرين حتى.
She almost screwed you over.
كادت أن تدمرك.
Stop talking about others.
توقف عن الحديث عن الآخرين.
Let's talk about you.
لنتحدث عنك.
About me?
عني؟
I'm doing fine.
أنا بخير.
Don't play dumb.
لا تلعب الغبي.
How are you doing
كيف حالك
with Tan Shen?
مع تان شين؟
Let nature take its course.
ترك الطبيعة تأخذ مجراها.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I don't care
لا أهتم
who you're seeing.
من تراه.
But
ولكن
I have one more thing to remind you.
لدي شيء آخر لتذكيرك.
Don't get too involved in anything.
لا تتورط في أي شيء.
Before getting too invested,
قبل أن تستثمر كثيرًا ،
think about whether it's worth it.
فكر فيما إذا كان الأمر يستحق ذلك.
It's worth it.
انه يستحق ذلك.
Are you so sure?
هل أنت متأكد جدا؟
He's nice.
انه لطيف.
Nice?
لطيف - جيد؟
What's good about him?
ما الجيد فيه؟
When I first met him,
عندما قابلته لأول مرة ،
I thought he was ruthless.
اعتقدت أنه كان قاسيا.
But when I got to know him,
لكن عندما تعرفت عليه ،
I found
وجدت
that he's quite genuine.
أنه حقيقي تمامًا.
There's a hero
هناك بطل
living in his heart.
يعيش في قلبه.
Do you really like him?
هل تحبه حقًا؟
I do.
أفعل.
I just got the news.
لقد تلقيت الأخبار للتو.
Qiu Zhijian turned himself in
سلم Qiu Zhijian نفسه
and took all the blame.
وأخذ كل اللوم.
He took all the blame?
أخذ كل اللوم؟
Doesn't that mean Fang Jianshe
لا يعني ذلك فانغ جيانشي
managed to get away?
تمكنت من الابتعاد؟
I'm going back to the firm tomorrow.
سأعود إلى الشركة غدا.
Let me ask Mr. Xu about the situation.
اسمحوا لي أن أسأل السيد شو عن الوضع.
He should
يجب عليه
know it better.
تعرف ذلك بشكل أفضل.
[Lu Yang]
[لو يانغ]
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Speak.
يتكلم.
Fang Jianshe.
فانغ جيانشي.
You're really something.
أنت حقا شيء.
Do you think you'll be fine
هل تعتقد أنك ستكون بخير
if you ask Qiu Zhijian
إذا سألت Qiu Zhijian
to take the blame?
لتحمل اللوم؟
Don't forget
لا تنسى
that I have something against you with me.
أن لدي شيئًا ضدي معي.
Let me remind you again.
اسمحوا لي أن أذكرك مرة أخرى.
Give me all the money now.
أعطني كل المال الآن.
Or
أو
I'll hand it over.
سوف أسلمها.
At that time,
فى ذلك التوقيت،
someone will kill you.
سيقتلك شخص ما.
You're Xia Xinliang, right?
أنت شيا شين ليانغ ، أليس كذلك؟
Drop the act.
إسقاط الفعل.
I know you're Xia Xinliang.
أعلم أنك شيا شين ليانغ.
Do you know
هل تعرف
what I found in the car?
ماذا وجدت في السيارة؟
It must not be that list.
يجب ألا تكون تلك القائمة.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
you won't pretend
لن تتظاهر
to be Xu Youning.
ليكون شو يونغ.
Are you sure?
هل أنت واثق؟
Not only am I sure,
لست متأكدًا فقط ،
but I also know that Shen Nanqiu
لكنني أعلم أيضًا أن شين Nanqiu
is colluding with you.
يتواطأ معك.
I don't know what you're talking about.
لا أعرف ما الذي تتحدث عنه.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Then I'll say something
ثم سأقول شيئا
you can understand.
تستطيع ان تفهم.
Did Shen Nanqiu promise
هل وعد شين Nanqiu
to send you out?
لإرسالك؟
And she promised to share the money with you.
ووعدت بتقاسم المال معك.
Just give up.
استسلم فقط.
Shen Nanqiu
شين نانكيو
won't give you a penny.
لن يعطيك فلسا واحدا.
Sending you abroad?
أرسلك للخارج؟
She means to take you out.
إنها تعني إخراجك.
She plans to
انها تخطط ل
pin everything on you,
يعلق كل شيء عليك ،
so her hands will be clean.
فتكون يداها نظيفتين.
Nothing will be traced
لن يتم تعقب أي شيء
back to her.
العودة إليها.
Do you get it now?
هل حصلت عليها الان؟
She wouldn't dare.
لم تجرؤ.
I have the account number.
لدي رقم الحساب.
Are you sure
هل أنت واثق
the account is real?
الحساب حقيقي؟
♪Glancing up♪
♪ نظرة خاطفة
♪The night sky seemed to bloom like a flower♪
بدت سماء الليل وكأنها تتفتح مثل الزهرة ♪
♪Subzero temperature♪
♪ درجة حرارة تحت الصفر ♪
♪Flying alone, wandering♪
تحلق بمفردك ، تائه ♪
♪Without a direction♪
♪ بدون اتجاه ♪
♪You look at me♪
♪ أنت تنظر إلي ♪
♪As if I were an injured lamb♪
كأنني خروف مجروح
♪I peer at you♪
أنا أنظير إليك ♪
♪Like fireworks, burning bright♪
♪ مثل الألعاب النارية ، حرق مشرق ♪
♪You describe how heaven is with your silence♪
أنت تصف كيف تكون الجنة بصمتك
♪I pretend to be captivated, the corners of my lips upturned♪
♪ أتظاهر بأنني مفتون ، زوايا شفتي مقلوبة
♪You walk towards me♪
أنت تمشي نحوي ♪
♪Like the moonlight peeking through the tears♪
♪ مثل ضوء القمر الذي يطل من خلال الدموع ♪
♪I hold onto you♪
♪ أنا متمسّك بك ♪
♪Like a wish fulfilled amongst the despair♪
كأمنية تتحقق بين اليأس
♪Although the moth is drawn to the flame♪
♪ على الرغم من انجذاب العثة إلى اللهب ♪
♪Since the smoke is still warm and the night is still young♪
بما أن الدخان لا يزال دافئًا والليل ما زال فتيًا
♪Let it burn♪
دعها تحترق ♪
♪You look at me♪
♪ أنت تنظر إلي ♪
♪As if I were an injured lamb♪
كأنني خروف مجروح
♪I peer at you♪
أنا أنظير إليك ♪
♪Like fireworks, burning bright♪
♪ مثل الألعاب النارية ، حرق مشرق ♪
♪You describe how heaven is with your silence♪
أنت تصف كيف تكون الجنة بصمتك
♪I pretend to be captivated, the corners of my lips upturned♪
♪ أتظاهر بأنني مفتون ، زوايا شفتي مقلوبة
♪You walk towards me♪
أنت تمشي نحوي ♪
♪Like the moonlight peeking through the tears♪
♪ مثل ضوء القمر الذي يطل من خلال الدموع ♪
♪I hold onto you♪
♪ أنا متمسّك بك ♪
♪Like a wish fulfilled amongst the despair♪
كأمنية تتحقق بين اليأس
♪Although the moth is drawn to the flame♪
♪ على الرغم من انجذاب العثة إلى اللهب ♪
♪Since the smoke is still warm and the night is still young♪
بما أن الدخان لا يزال دافئًا والليل ما زال فتيًا
♪Let it burn♪
دعها تحترق ♪